talk about what jeido secrets I need to
谈论我需要的jeido秘密
explain more what no sicko means
解释更多没有病态的意思
basically those secrets are technology
基本上那些秘密是技术
to store storage information so it's the
存储存储信息，因此
exactly something that SQL database does
正是SQL数据库所做的事情
so I can put information there I can
所以我可以把信息放在那里
retry information there I can delete
重试我可以删除的信息
information there so I can do a large
那里的信息，所以我可以做大
stuff with no Seco technology but to
没有山高技术的东西，但是
have some difference right now because
现在有些不同，因为
right now I have with five different
现在我有五个不同的
types
类型
I have no standard yet and I have no
我还没有标准，也没有
transaction and they normally don't use
交易，他们通常不使用
structure like SQL
像SQL这样的结构
let's go deeply on the types the first
让我们先深入了解第一种类型
word a key value so we have the most
讲一个关键值，以便我们拥有最大的价值
famous one in Redis so I believe
我相信Redis中的著名人物
everyone he is a Java developer so the
他都是Java开发人员，所以
key value has the same structure as
键值的结构与
hashmap so I have a key and to this key
哈希图，所以我有一个密钥，并为此密钥
I have has the key value so that is it I
我拥有关键价值，就是我
can return formation for the key and
可以返回密钥的形式，并且
there is death in that is it I have the
有死亡，就是我有
document so the most famous one in my
文件是我中最著名的
opinion is the Monte B so this structure
意见是Monte B，所以这个结构
is something like JSON as JSON file or
是像JSON这样的JSON文件或
XML file so basically the whole idea is
XML文件，所以基本上整个想法是
I have a collection of the document and
我有一份文件的收藏，
this collection has document and this
这个收藏有文件，这个
document has a topple the stop is a a
文件倒塌是一个
key where the key is the the name of the
键，其中键是名称
information in the value and that is the
价值中的信息，那就是
information in the sample here I have
我这里的样本中的信息
the key first name and the value John I
关键名字和值John I
have the key last name in the value is
值中的关键姓为
Miss in the document I have the sub
我在文件中的小姐
document concept so archaic input
文档概念如此过时的输入
document inside documents so I have the
里面的文件，所以我有
document address and I put more document
文件地址，我放了更多文件
inside
内
dress that's the whole idea on the
着装就是整个想法
document structure let's go in deeply to
文档结构让我们深入了解
: family so I have the column family
：家庭，所以我有专栏家庭
here
这里
I hope everyone knows what Cassandra is
我希望每个人都知道卡桑德拉是什么
but Cassandra is one implementation of :
但是Cassandra是以下一种实现：
family it is looks similar to column so
家庭，它看起来类似于列，所以
I have my column family at the top and
我的专栏家庭在顶部，
they have column and the column is is
他们有专栏，专栏是
composed by a topo so the topo is keep
由地形组成，因此地形保持
value the key is the name value is a
值键是名称值是
right formation and one important thing
正确的形成和一件重要的事情
he stuff here is the column is clearly
他在这里的东西是专栏显然
created just in time so if you take a
及时创建，所以如果您
look here I have a Paulo it has very and
看这里，我有一个Paulo，它有非常
just after it has color because the
刚好有颜色，因为
information was created just in time
信息是及时创建的
that's a little different of the sko
这与sko有点不同
technology because if you have
技术，因为如果您有
information or not the column is stood
信息是否站立
there with information or with is new
有信息或有新
value that's the idea okay right now I
值，这是个好主意，现在我
have the grass and no secret database
有草，没有秘密数据库
basically a kink save relationship
基本上是纽结保存关系
between
之间
vertex so I have the Apollo a are
顶点，所以我有阿波罗
artists both are brothers and I have
艺术家俩都是兄弟，我有
kratos I told them nerd so Kratos queue
kratos我告诉他们书呆子，所以Kratos排队
Apollo and Kratos peel ours believe
阿波罗和克雷托斯剥夺了我们的信念
everyone who knows what god of warriors
每个知道什么战士神的人
playstation ok basically i keep the the
Playstation好的，基本上我保持
relationship between this guy here who
这家伙在这里的关系谁
knows netflix linkage ii okay basically
基本上知道netflix联动ii
to to disciplic edge to gesso informatio
到门徒优势到gesso信息
okay this guy has something in common
好吧，这个家伙有一些共同点
with you basically they try to use some
基本上和他们一起尝试使用一些
graph databases of that and i have the
图的数据库，我有
last one that's a mood model what
最后一个是情绪模型
multi-model means basically on oseco
多模型意味着基本上在oseco上
provider has mod support modern one type
提供商具有mod支持现代的一种类型
it's a moot model so our NDB support
这是一个模拟模型，因此我们的NDB支持
graph and document cut base key value
图形和文档剪切的基本键值
and document so if it has bar to model
并记录文件，以便它具有建模的酒吧
one type
一种
it's a mooch model the trivial
这是一个琐碎的模型
relationship normally when you try to
关系，当您尝试
use no sicko
不使用镰刀
you try to do analogy with the SQL
您尝试使用SQL做类比
technology so let's take a look in this
技术，让我们来看看
structure if take a look and key value
外观和关键值的结构
that's the simplest one so I have the
那是最简单的一个，所以我有
bucket and a key value pair and the
存储桶和一个键值对以及
document I have the collection the
我收集的文件
document and the document has a topo
文档和文档中有一个topo
that's a key in value so he is the name
这是价值的关键，所以他是名字
in value the information the surfing in
有价值的信息在网上冲浪
a column and no one guy she is just as
一列，没有人像她一样
Cal has relationship so joins lefty
卡尔有关系，所以加入左撇子
joins are the joints and the graph is
连接是关节，图形是
totally different so the first advice
完全不同，所以第一个建议
you if I'd let you use no Seco don't try
你，如果我让你不使用山高，请不要尝试
to emulate SQL and ocq database because
模拟SQL和OCQ数据库，因为
the project gonna fail okay let's just
该项目将失败，好吧，我们只是
look in a single application if you are
在单个应用程序中查看
using Java EE application with SQL
结合使用Java EE应用程序和SQL
technology so I have JP a data standards
技术，所以我有JP数据标准
so I have JDBC data standards you so
所以我有JDBC数据标准
what happened if I'd like to change my C
如果我想更改我的C会发生什么
code to post we own the java application
发布我们拥有的Java应用程序的代码
what I need to do
我需要做什么
yeah just I just need to change the
是的，我只需要更改
driver right so no codes to change
驾驶员正确，因此无需更改代码
basically just a driver and imagine
基本上只是一个驾驶员，想象
imagine right now I mean using urban
想象现在我的意思是使用城市
native limitation and you like to use
本机限制，您喜欢使用
open egb from patchy what I need to
从斑驳的地方打开egb我需要
change just the implementation because
仅更改实现，因为
the API going to be exactly the same
API将完全相同
that's advanced a few standards but it's
这已经提高了一些标准，但是
not going to happen no sick application
不会发生没有生病的申请
because there's no stuttered there so if
因为那里没有口吃，所以如果
I may use Cassandra and let you use
我可能会使用Cassandra，让您使用
HBase I'm going to break me my towel or
HBase我要折断我的毛巾或
my poster if I may use the moment it be
我的海报，如果我可以使用的话
I'd like to use Couchbase I need to
我想使用需要的Couchbase
change my my API is because it both has
更改我的API是因为两者都有
different API we right now we have some
我们现在有一些不同的API
solution to solve this kind of stuff so
解决这类问题的方法
we have spring data who those bring data
我们有 spring data ，那些数据带来了
oh nice and we have our Veneto Jim and
哦，很好，我们有威尼托·吉姆和
top link I will in spring the data is
我将在春季的顶部链接数据是
the most famous one to solve integration
解决集成最著名的
between no Seco in java application and
在Java应用程序中没有Seco和
we have our bonito GM and top link
我们有鱼总经理和顶部链接
basically our Benes try to you the same
基本上我们的Benes会尽力向您
api the same JPA API to to connect with
api要连接的相同JPA API
no Seco database basically I have JP a
没有山高数据库，基本上我有JP
to connect with Cassandra to connect we
与Cassandra连接以连接我们
have mom DB this does sound a nice idea
让妈妈DB听起来不错
because I don't need to learn a new API
因为我不需要学习新的API
but I have problem used that right
但我有问题使用该权利
because JP a was not made to know sick
因为JP a不是让他知道生病
database so I cannot save as
数据库，所以我无法另存为
synchronously I cannot save you CTL the
同步我无法保存您的CTL
time to live in in all secure database
时间存放在所有安全数据库中
we have a lot of diversity in the
我们在
diversity really matter to us so if
多样性对我们真的很重要，所以如果
every using Cassandra are you like to
每个使用Cassandra的人都想
use Cassandra query language
使用Cassandra查询语言
if every using Couchbase I'd like to use
如果每个我都想使用Couchbase
like a query if you'd like I'd like to
如果您想我想查询
use a large search a large search has
使用大型搜索大型搜索
certain genes that I'd like to use and
我想要使​​用的某些基因
so I mean using MongoDB Modi behaves
所以我的意思是使用MongoDB Modi的行为
feature that just moong the be has so
只是moong be be具有的功能
specifically behavior a no sick database
专门表现没有病的数据库
really matter
非常重要
that's a total different of the FQ
与FQ完全不同
technology so the first channel
技术是第一个渠道
challenging on no sick technology is the
没有生病的技术带来的挑战是
diversity because the reverse see really
多样性，因为反向看真的
matter so we have different types who
重要的是，我们有不同类型的人
have different goals we have different
有不同的目标我们有不同的目标
behaviors we have different proposals we
行为，我们有不同的建议，我们
have different ways to communicate you
有不同的沟通方式
to communicate if no secure database so
如果没有安全的数据库则进行通信
have p2p webmasters live after different
让p2p网站站长过后
ways to do that so to try to solve that
解决问题的方法
we create the jano psycho proposal so
我们创建了贾诺心理建议
they they the idea is okay let's have
他们他们的想法还好，让我们有
two layers the first one going to be in
两层，第一层将在
the mapping layer so something like JPA
映射层，例如JPA
does and in fact what you use and they I
确实，实际上您使用的是什么，我
have communication layers something that
有沟通层的东西
database it does so I have two different
数据库，所以我有两个不同
layers to want to and I kind I can do
想要的层次，我可以做到
divide and conquer
分而治之
why that because I can have the no sicko
为什么那样，因为我可以没有病
providers on one layer I can have the no
一层上的提供程序我可以没有
single providers working on
单一提供商在工作
communication layer because they don't
通讯层，因为他们不
succumb to no sicko providers just the
屈服于没有病态的提供者
communication matter so this guy can
沟通很重要，所以这个人可以
work just a communication layer and to
只是一个通信层而已
solution guys such as P photo with
解决方案专家，例如P photo与
spring Arvind age with redhead with
春季Arvind年龄与红发
urban age just a mapping layer matter so
城市时代只是一个映射层很重要
I can divide and conquer so these guys
我可以分开征服所以这些家伙
can work together and different goals
可以一起工作和不同的目标
and no low key because right now you're
而且没有低调，因为现在你是
going to have four different API so what
将有四个不同的API，那又如何
API two column one API few key value
API两列一API几个关键值
or FBI to grasp and you want to be a
或FBI掌握，您想成为
document so have four different api's to
文档，因此具有四个不同的api
try to solve four different documents so
尝试解决四个不同的文件，所以
what what happened with mooch motto if a
如果一个人的座右铭发生了什么
know singular abate has sport modern
知道单数减少有现代运动
type its modules to implement module
输入其模块以实施模块
don't want type so codebase hair sports
不想打字，所以代码库的头发运动
a document addressed so it's must
解决的文件，所以必须
implement document and graph the idea so
实施文件并用图形表示想法
right now general Seco is I Eclipse in
现在山高将军是我在
foundation project so it's a dog dual
基础项目，所以它是狗双
license so a party and a clip see the
许可，因此聚会和剪辑请参见
idea is okay I have a comb API
想法还可以，我有梳状API
oh no sicko but the the different
哦，没有病，但与众不同
behavioral matters so I have extensible
行为问题，所以我可以扩展
I have extension to use this specific
我可以扩展使用此特定
behavior and why Diana were Artemis
行为以及戴安娜为何成为阿尔emi弥斯
basically my product my name so basic I
基本上我的产品我的名字这么基本我
love history
爱情史
so I puts name that is it our adventure
所以我把名字叫做我们的冒险
I have the communication layer the Diana
我有Diana的通讯层
so I have four different api's let's
所以我有四种不同的API
take just a really simple here I have
我这里有一个非常简单的方法
four different no SICU database so our
四个不同的无SICU数据库，因此我们
guy here our documents no Seco so I have
家伙这里我们的文件没有山高所以我有
our remedy be I have multi be I have
我们的补救措施是我有多重
codebase and I have already be if you
代码库，如果您已经
take a look the code they are totally
看一看它们完全是什么代码
different right so I have the base
不同的权利，所以我有基础
document to our MTB I have document
文件到我们的MTB我有文件
among to be but if you take look deeply
在其中，但是如果你看得更深
deeply they behavior going to be the
深深地，他们的行为将是
same because I have my collection and
同样，因为我有我的收藏，
let you put one document in the document
让您将一个文件放入文件中
has a key value where the key is the
有一个键值，其中键是
name and the value is the information
名称和值是信息
right so take a look here base document
对，所以在这里看一下基本文件
age at a table so the beta tribute is
在餐桌上的年龄，因此beta敬意是
name in value the document append so
在文件中附加值名称，以便附加
name value Jason put name value
名称值Jason放置名称值
a document feels David value so
文件觉得David很有价值，所以
basically what like to do is put a
基本上喜欢做的是
document there so we don't need this we
在那里记录，所以我们不需要这个
just need a comb API to solve these
只需要一个梳子API来解决这些
problems
问题
so that's the whole idea so I created my
这就是整个想法，所以我创建了我的
document entity and akavir created my
文档实体和akavir创建了我的
document that has name in value the key
值中具有名称的文档密钥
value the topic and then put this
重视话题，然后把这个
document in my entity and this API is
我实体中的文档，此API是
gonna implement that idea and also try
要实现这个想法，然后尝试
to solve the Nemec lecture because we
解决Nemec讲座，因为我们
have a lot of literature to do the
有很多文献要做
exactly same thing so I have inserts
完全一样的东西，所以我有插入
save delete with remove update merge
用删除更新合并保存删除
find search alert stuff the something
查找搜索警报的东西
happened with time to leave so I have
发生有时间离开，所以我有
long two seconds in two seconds long to
在两秒钟之内长到两秒钟
my seconds into my second so basically I
我的秒数几乎是我的第二秒
have different ways to do this Akal
有不同的方法来做到这一点
something
某事
oh that's a whole idea so I my Diane
哦，那是个完整的主意，所以我是我的黛安
approach has four different api's four
方法有四个不同的api的四个
different STC keys that is technical
不同的技术性STC密钥
compatibility kit so I have mine that
兼容性套件，所以我有
database I have my API API there I
数据库中有我的API API
implement run my tck it's okay it's
实施运行我的tck，没关系，这是
going to support they don't make lecture
要支持他们不讲课
I try to use the same name macro tool on
我尝试在上使用相同的名称宏工具
the APA when I can and of course the
我可以的时候APA当然
diversity really matter I will make sure
多样性真的很重要，我会确保
before so I have here my column entity I
之前，所以我在这里有我的专栏实体
created to create some columns so I can
创建以创建一些列，以便我可以
save with multiple implementation so
保存多个实现，以便
spectral here my save API can save as
在这里光谱我的保存API可以另存为
Cassandra HBase for example but I can't
以Cassandra HBase为例，但我做不到
wait extension in this case with
在这种情况下等待扩展
Cassandra because yes cassandra has
卡桑德拉，因为是的卡桑德拉有
secured because the key out means
之所以安全，是因为密钥意味着
cassandra clare language so
卡桑德拉克莱尔语所以
merci really matter on oseco database we
Merci对oseco数据库真的很重要
have a lot of providers walking this
有很多供应商走这条路
product right now so I have we have
产品，现在我拥有
Cassandra cut Bayes multi be Oracle
卡桑德拉切贝叶斯成为甲骨文
eight basil hello class
八罗勒你好课
finca pork a lot of guys we have
芬卡猪肉我们有很多人
communities work with us right now so we
社区现在与我们合作，所以我们
have spring data guys we have some Java
有 spring data 专家，我们有一些Java
Java Bahia a lot of Java C groups maybe
Java Bahia可能有很多Java C组
the future
未来
this job is a group will give us
这个工作是一个团队会给我们的
feedback about the - about the API okay
关于的反馈-关于API可以了
I make sure I have two layers
我确保我有两层
communication layer that's a Gianna and
通讯层是Gianna和
Artemis basically is CDI + communication
Artemis基本上是CDI +交流
layer basically the idea is okay let's
基本上，这个想法是可以的
put mapping annotation and on my object
将贴图注释放在我的对象上
here and our time is gonna convert to
在这里，我们的时间将转化为
communication layer that's the whole
整个通信层
idea of Artemis so I can put a lot of
Artemis的想法，所以我可以放很多
stuff here dynamic query so basically I
这里的东西动态查询所以基本上我
can do queries use using methods and
可以使用方法和
interface and Artemis can cared to do
界面和Artemis可以照顾
this query to you I can put a lot of
这个查询给你我可以放很多
events I can observe on even for them to
我甚至可以观察到的事件
put be validation
验证
ow I already mentioned before the
哦，我之前已经提到过
diversity really marital matter so I
多样性真的很重要，所以我
have a lot of attention so in scale here
有很多关注，所以这里规模很大
I put the unity a notation you Unity
我把团结记为你团结
means user defined type of course that
表示用户定义的课程类型
is not the the coma API that's the
不是昏迷的API
extension API to Cassandra so just
扩展到Cassandra的API
concerned I can't stand you DT and the
我不能忍受你的DT和
something going to have with secure
安全的东西
because just Cassandra can send secure
因为只有Cassandra才能发送安全
because the key out means Cassandra
因为关键是Cassandra
query language that is our roadmap so we
查询这是我们的路线图，所以我们
have some code proposal we are doing
我们正在做一些代码建议
this to to receive feedback from
这是为了接收来自
community if
如果社区
is work or not try to move a lot of
是工作还是不尝试移动很多
those psycho vendors solution windows
那些心理供应商的解决方案窗口
guys put us a kiss products you have
伙计们给我们一个吻产品
developed a lot a lot of code and then
开发了很多代码，然后
created ideas are there da is too few
创造的想法太少了
years so on the Java EE 9 but I'm not
Java EE 9上已经有很多年了，但是我不是
sure Korea is so long time so I can't
确定韩国时间这么长，我不能
oldest that's going to happen or not but
是否会发生最古老的
I hope so and we have a site so I have J
希望如此，我们有一个网站，所以我有J
no secret art that can have a lot of
没有秘密艺术可以有很多
formation there we have all the code is
那里我们所有的代码是
open source so you came for work you can
开源，因此您可以上班
put star can go deeply in the codes of
放星星可以深入了解
open some issues please give us feedback
打开一些问题，请给我们反馈
in this product so we have mail lists we
在这个产品中，所以我们有邮件列表
have year we also have week so if you go
有一年，我们也有一周，所以如果你去
to the general secret arc you can get a
到一般的秘密弧，你可以得到一个
lot information there okay that is it
好多的信息就可以了
so right now let's do a demo with Gino
所以现在让我们与Gino做一个演示
Seco basically the idea is give a Java
山高基本上的想法是给Java
project a Java version products let's do
设计一个Java版本的产品让我们做
an integration between Java and no stick
Java与不粘手之间的集成
database in this case you are running
在这种情况下，数据库正在运行
the Couchbase database so basically I'm
Couchbase数据库，所以基本上我是
running Couchbase in the docker
在docker中运行Couchbase
container
容器
so if you look here I'm running talker I
所以如果你看这里我正在说话
created a document document collection
创建了一个文档文档集合
of heroes the idea is to put heroes here
英雄的想法是把英雄放在这里
of course so let's go to my job
当然，让我们去工作吧
application I have my entity
应用程序我有我的实体
so that's hero and my hero has some
那是英雄，我的英雄有一些
eight routes such as ID name real name
ID名实名等8条路线
age and powers and one person figure in
年龄和权力和一个人的身影
I appear different from SQL technology
我看起来与SQL技术不同
is because and I'll seek work in storage
是因为，我会去仓库工作
the entire collection it just want just
它只是想要的整个收藏而已
one document just one row if you going
一个文件，如果你要走的话，只有一行
to be a SEO technology you can see the
成为SEO技术，您可以看到
import import north from the APA but you
从APA进口进口，但是您
try to keep the SEM dimetric sure so
尽量确保SEM的二分法确保
have entity we have ID
有实体，我们有ID
we have column there's something that
我们有专栏有一些
the Jaypee ever does we have our hero
Jaypee曾经有我们的英雄
empty and we have the hero research
空了，我们有英雄研究
basically the idea is okay have my hero
基本上这个主意还可以
my hero model in let's put this model to
我的英雄模型让我们把这个模型
public as JSON and in the middle and
作为JSON公开，中间和
between the research and the JSON and my
在研究与JSON和我之间
model I created my presentation the idea
我创建演示文稿的模型
is to split what's going show to public
是将公开节目内容公开
our jax-rs and my model so for example
例如我们的jax-rs和我的模型
would like to hide the real name because
想隐藏真实姓名，因为
the identity of the hero is secret I
英雄的身份是秘密我
can't remove remove this line here but I
无法删除删除此行，但我
think keep saving in the database and to
认为继续保存在数据库中并
do this integration between my
在我之间进行整合
application and the database we have the
应用程序和数据库，我们拥有
my poster basically this guy is just on
我的海报基本上这个家伙就在
interface that extend my hero hip my hip
扩展我的英雄臀部的界面
holster this reporter is from our team
皮套记者来自我们的团队
so basically I have a common comments on
所以基本上我对
the post our interface and then I quit
发布我们的界面，然后我退出
it and you want you
它，你想要你
Meadows query so basically I can find by
草地查询，所以基本上我可以找到
name fun asier greater than and find a
命名大于，并找到一个
here lesser then so I can delete by name
然后在这里少一点，所以我可以按名称删除
basically I created some reader to query
基本上我创建了一些读者来查询
and delete just using no make secure the
并删除不使用使安全
madam so the art I'm just going to care
太太，所以我要去关心的艺术
what left to us stick you here you want
我们剩下的就是你想要的东西
to anything like and the foe hero a
对任何类似敌人的英雄
pulsar
脉冲星
oh you don't post our implementation
哦，您不发布我们的实施
because our times you wanna care to us
因为我们的时代你想照顾我们
this implementation so let's return to
这个实现，让我们回到
to my research so then see so I can find
我的研究，所以然后看，我可以找到
by ID use my hand pole star and then
通过ID用我的手杖星，然后
converts to my presentation and I can do
转换为我的演示文稿，我可以做
some queries a senior's Heroes test you
一些查询高级英雄测试你
older than some age young heroes I can
我比某些年龄的年轻英雄大
save hero is post merit and HTTP and
保存英雄是后功和HTTP和
update hero and of course delete hero so
更新英雄，当然删除英雄，所以
basically I'm reusing just job II
基本上我只是在重复工作II
technology stay glue here so just Java
技术就在这里，所以只用Java
EE technology anniversary Java EE 7 and
EE技术周年纪念Java EE 7和
I mean running there are teams and as
我的意思是说，有团队合作，
mentioned before I have the driver the
在我有司机之前提到
guy gonna do the connection between
家伙会做之间的联系
application and oseco so I just have to
应用程序和oseco，所以我只需要
on my application just got here just I
在我的应用程序刚到这里
have the kind that's localhost and the
具有localhost和
user and the password and
用户和密码以及
everything else and searches okay I'd
其他的一切都可以，我会搜索
like to define my collection so
喜欢定义我的收藏，所以
basically just using CDI so I created my
基本上只使用CDI，所以我创建了我的
configuration to read the information
配置读取信息
for the profits I created created my
我创造的利润创造了我的
factor and then I committed my manager
因素，然后我承诺我的经理
and my manager care the heroes document
我的经理照顾英雄文件
collection so based on that and my he
因此，基于他和我的收藏
posts our interface the items gonna care
在我们的界面上发布将要处理的项目
every everything else just using CDI
所有其他一切都仅使用CDI
okay another point is I'm using Tommy
好的，我要使用汤米
sever and Tommy broke it plugging so I
切断，汤米打破了堵塞，所以我
came running as fecha and actually
像fecha一样跑来跑去，实际上
that's what are you gonna do so
那就是你要做的
basically I compile the code using maven
基本上我使用maven编译代码
and then run Tommy
然后运行汤米
okay that's running so fast by day to
好吧，每天运行如此之快
make either and fast instead I create
使两者兼而有之，我创建
some script so this idea behind the
一些脚本，所以这个想法背后
screen should be basically I create some
屏幕基本上应该是我创建的
post metals using curve so to save some
使用曲线发布金属，以节省一些
information there at the cloud base
云基础上的信息
right now let's empty let's do a refresh
现在让我们清空让我们刷新
show to you there's no information there
向您显示那里没有信息
and let's run the script if with some
如果有的话让我们运行脚本
heroes and basically it's a post battle
英雄，基本上是后期战斗
battle so I'm going to save a large guys
战斗，所以我要救一个大家伙
a lot of heroes so right now we have
很多英雄，所以现在我们有
that
那
the breadwinner we know kept America and
我们知道养家糊口的人使美国和
hook have some heroes of course so
钩当然有一些英雄
basically let's show some queries so I
基本上让我们显示一些查询，所以我
can find my ID okay
可以找到我的身份证
just use get I can find some heroes
只是使用得到我可以找到一些英雄
seniors and the zero is odors older than
老年人和零是气味比
turn two years old so Vince Camuto and
快两岁了，所以文斯·卡穆托（Vince Camuto）和
chala Natasha Romanov chief Rogers and
查拉·娜塔莎·罗曼诺夫（Chala Natasha Romanov）首席罗杰斯（Rogers）和
don't talk and I can find youngers done
不要说话，我可以找到年轻人
some age so basically the idea is a
某个年龄，所以基本上这个想法是
simple integration between Java and no
Java和no之间的简单集成
sequel database and of course with some
续集数据库，当然还有一些
extension to use also the specific
扩展使用还具体
behavior from a physicist database again
再次从物理学家数据库获取行为
we have the website that J no secret art
我们的网站上没有J的秘密艺术
oops so have some information here the
糟糕，所以在这里有一些信息
concept here to tell you about the
这里的概念告诉你有关
layers and some data be that we are
层和一些数据是
supporting right now some simple using
现在支持一些简单的使用
just the communication layer that's all
仅仅是通信层
Diana and abstraction layer that map
戴安娜和映射的抽象层
layers and take our name so follow us on
层，并取我们的名字，所以跟随我们
Twitter tweets at Otago Java and the
Twitter在Otago Java和
product has a Twitter account data as
产品的Twitter帐户数据为
you know Seco that's it thank you
你知道山高就是这样谢谢